

Nhung Nguyễn

INTERNAL COMMUNICATION OFFICER

- **6** 08891 13579
- hongnhungts1412@gmail.co m
- https://www.facebook.com/hongnhungts14122001/
- Lane 2, Thang Long Avenue,
 Nam Tu Liem District, Hanoi
 Capital

SKILLS -

OFFICE COMPUTER SKILL
Proficient in the use of Word,
Excel, Powerpoint, Canva.

ENGLISH ABILITY

- Fluent English
 Communication.
- Ability in listening, speaking, reading and writing in English.
- Ability to collect information in English.

With specialized knowledge and related knowledge having learned before and hard work, I hope I will have the opportunity to accompany your company. I am confident in myself able to take initiative in work and complete tasks delivered as best as possible.

WORK EXPERIENCE -

MARKETING INTERN

11/2022 - 5/2023

Global Study Partners

- In charge of content and online campaigns for new products & new school.
- Support to communicate with different vendors (education agency, school, university) to deliver the content. Assisting management team to manage upcoming projects in Vietnam.
- Management Fanpage, social network accounts.
- Perform various tasks as directly by the director.

COLLABORATOR

3/2021 - 12/2021

MyGu company

- Support to find collaborators to survey customers in the field shopping area on electronic websites.
- Synthesize and statistics the costumes imported from the orderssupplier and quantity sold.

TELESALE 10/2020 - 2/2021

Babylons Company

- · Call to consult customers about business courses.
- Receive and respond to students' questions related to regarding the course.
- Statistics of the number of students consulted and questions from students .

EDUCATION —

INTERNATIONAL RELATION AND GLOBAL COMMUNICATION

2020 - 2024

University: Academy of Journalism and Communication

The major in International Relations and Global Communication provides students with in-depth international relations knowledge and skills, along with international journalism, diplomacy, foreign affairs, and global communication skills global (Including: media management and international media products), specialized English. The goal is to train generations of students who are dynamic and have good foreign language skills to meet the increasing requirements of society.